

About me

I'm a programmer professional with expertise in both development and IT support. With experience in JavaScript, PHP, Vue.js and SQL, I have strong teamwork skills and a commitment to continuous improvement.

contact



064-870-5113



hotzang55@gmail.com



55 Boonpathan Khaolam Road Sansuk Sub-districtt, Muang District, Chonburi, 20130

Education

- Rajamangala University of Technology Rattanakosin |2018-2021
- Bachelor of Engineering in Computer Engineering GPA 2.57

Skill

- Html And Css
- Python
- C
- Javascript
- Vue.js
- PHP

- SQL
- Lalavel (PHP)
- vnc viewer
- Anydesk
- Microsoft Office
- SQL workbench

Language

- English (Intermediate)
- Thai (Native)

Jirawat Paktawee

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER



Work Experience

Total Digital Innovation

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER | JAN 2022 - PRESENT

- Test the hardware devices that will be used in the system.
- Develop websites according to customer needs such as
 - Summary of admin and customer dashboards
 - Create the system's check-in and check-out page.
 - Website reporting system
 - Make a summary of results and display them as Statistics with charts
- Support IT problems of internal employees in the company
- Assemble computers and install operating systems
- Remote to solve system problems for customers
- Stock system products for the company
- CRM system
- The system summarizes the results of overtime parking reports.
- Job Save Management System
- Coupon management system with purchases connected to Line Line OA

KEEP CODING CO., LTD.(INTERNSHIP)

WEB DEVELOPER | NOV 2019 - MAR 2020

- Design CRM system according to customer's requirements.
- Fix system operation errors according to customer requirements.
- Add and edit information travel in the application via Ionic